{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"kovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"druga","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kau","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nave","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ekivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sveu","osnova2":"ilište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"kafi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sino","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sljede","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"uop","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
